On today's video we're going to make
Ultra Luxury coffee ice cream that
matches Häagen Dazs' own.... actually is
better..... there's a few ingredients to
it but it is pretty simple yes you can make
this in a ninja creamy let's get started.
So what are we going to need for this ice
cream well we are going to just make this
a cold process apart from the coffee obviously
that's going to be hot but we're going to use
Guam or Guam as I like to say because that's cold
process stabilizer and it's hot enough as it is I
don't need to turn the oven oven I don't need to
turn any other heat sources on in the house right
now so let's get everything in we need 135g of
milk, 450g of cream, we're going to needed 175g of
espresso so that's there I use espresso pods it's
four of those to get that weight you might have
to change it depending on what one you got but
irrelevant but before we add that we're going
to add the rest of the ingredients so we need
130g of sugar, we need 40g of dextrose, 65g of
of skim milk powder, a tablespoon of skim milk
powder in a small .....o smack!.... in a little
Tupperware and we're going to add in our 1g of
guar gum into that we're then going to add our 1g
of pink himalayan salt just combine that together
if you don't want to use a stabilizer do use the
salt put that in there and
stir we need to stir this to
dissolve the sugars into our liquid
as it as it's quite a high fat recipe it
might take a minute or two of stirring but
it will and also this allows for the milk
powder to hydrate properly but we're going
to leave this in the fridge for about an
hour just to make sure that milk powder
completely hydrates right now while we're
stirring we're going to add in our coffee
if you're unsure if your sugar has dissolved
just take a spoon and just run it along the
bottom and you will feel the sugar crystals if
it's in there Quick Test delicious lid on in the
fridge for 1 hour quick tidy up and then I'll
come back in an hour when we're ready to churn.
So after your mix has been in the fridge for
an hour making sure that skim milk powder is
fully hydrated, we're going to take it out and
give it one final stir we just want to make sure
that everything is completely homogenized we want
all of those ingredients to go into our ice cream
machine always stir your base before you put it
in because you might have a skin or a layer on
the top and that needs to be reincorporated
before you put it in your ice cream machine
I've seen so many people just pour it in and
you get these horrible lumps in your ice cream
so don't do that anyway let's pour our ice
cream into our machine and get that machine
running after about 15 to 20 minutes, depending
on your machine, it should be ready I like to
take it out so it's nice and easy to scoop get
it in your container get that decorated with a
few chocolate covered coffee beans we're going to
pop it straight in the freezer and let it harden
off for a few hours it's been about 4 or 5 hours
taking it out of the freezer now it feel feels
about right have a look at the surface of that
lovely multicolor coffee beans we're going to get
some dished up into a bowl so let's have a look
and see what this consistency turned out like it
Scoops beautifully look how creamy and delicious
that looks the smell of that strong coffee coming
out oh I'm really really looking forward to having
this one a few more chocolate covered coffee beans
to finish and let's try it so there we go my
version ofand dar's coffee ice cream decorated
with some chocolate covered coffee beans they're
called espresso beans but you know it smells
delicious super creamy Ultra smooth real
coffee flavor that's the big standout
hen coffee ice cream has got real coffee
flavor whether they actually use coffee
itself or they've got some other
means to do it couldn't tell you
but this beets haand coffee ice cream
hands down glorious could eat this all
day I've already eaten a bowl of Biscoff ice
cream from the creamy this morning filming
multiples on one day but incredibly good coffee
ice cream like I said super smooth no ice crystals
really nice pungent coffee flavor real
coffee flavor you don't have to use the
pods that's just what I use because I've
got it here you can Brew up filter coffee
whatever coffee you want to use just make
sure it's strong you you want that as much
coffee flavor in that amount of liquid as
you can but there we go H remake thanks
very much for watching don't forget to like And
subscribe and I will see you next time [Music]